<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Ella</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/" />
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/atom.xml" />
    <id>tag:blog.youre.space,2017-01-31:/imyagirl//17</id>
    <updated>2017-02-26T14:41:20Z</updated>
    <subtitle>Your thoughts, my thoughts exactly.</subtitle>
    <generator uri="http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/">Movable Type 6.3</generator>

<entry>
    <title>Weather</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/2017/02/weather.html" />
    <id>tag:blog.youre.space,2017:/imyagirl//17.527</id>

    <published>2017-02-26T08:51:46Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-26T14:41:20Z</updated>

    <summary>The strange effect the weather has on a person is intriguing. Lately, somewhere between the winter and spring have dawned upon us. The short month of February brought various kinds of weather, from cold air to warm sunshine. On a...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Ella Chung</name>
        
    </author>
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/">
        <![CDATA[<p>The strange effect the weather has on a person is intriguing. Lately, somewhere between the winter and spring have dawned upon us. The short month of February brought various kinds of weather, from cold air to warm sunshine. On a sunny day, a person might feel warmth or hope. The cold, windy days make us realize the winter is not ready to leave us just yet. The cold wind brushes upon our faces, less willing inside.</p>
<p>Lately, the dusty days have been occuring more than all of us like. The warmer the days get, the heavier the dusts get. On a warm, sunny day, where people ought to enjoy themselves, are bothered by dusts changing the way we feel. Not being able to breathe in the fresh air we all desire, only leaves confusion and hatred.</p>
<p>The nature has its own way of giving us the grateful feeling inside. As the new season nears, hoping we would be able to savor every bit of the weather.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>첫번째</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/2017/01/post.html" />
    <id>tag:blog.youre.space,2017:/imyagirl//17.473</id>

    <published>2017-01-30T15:31:41Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-31T14:36:17Z</updated>

    <summary>글입니다. 앞으로 여보가 글 많이 써줄 겁니다. 흐흫...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Ella Chung</name>
        
    </author>
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/">
        글입니다. 앞으로 여보가 글 많이 써줄 겁니다. 흐흫
        
    </content>
</entry>

</feed>
