<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <title>Ella</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/" />
    <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/atom.xml" />
    <id>tag:blog.youre.space,2017-01-31:/imyagirl//17</id>
    <updated>2017-06-28T06:56:01Z</updated>
    <subtitle>Your thoughts, my thoughts exactly.</subtitle>
    <generator uri="http://www.sixapart.com/movabletype/">Movable Type 6.3.4</generator>

<entry>
    <title>Gathering Blue Review</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/2017/06/gathering-blue-review.html" />
    <id>tag:blog.youre.space,2017:/imyagirl//17.612</id>

    <published>2017-06-28T06:56:01Z</published>
    <updated>2017-06-28T06:56:01Z</updated>

    <summary>Gathering Blue by Lois Lowry is the second book in The Giver Quartet. Just like the first book, this book sets in the same future time. In the future there&apos;s a villege, a confounded villege where no one can express...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Ella Chung</name>
        
    </author>
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/">
        <![CDATA[<p>Gathering Blue  by Lois Lowry is the second book in The Giver Quartet. Just<br />
like the first book, this book sets in the same future time.</p>

<p>In the future there's a villege, a confounded villege where no one can<br />
express freedom. People are drilled with chores, and heavily damaged in<br />
many ways. Kira, a strong and courageous girl faces her life with audacity.<br />
Kira is born with a deformed leg. When her mother dies, she is left with<br />
nothing. Her mother had taught her how to weave, work with thread since she<br />
was young. The skill of weaving "came" to her as long as she can remember<br />
and this ability allows her to land on an important job. Throughout the<br />
story, she meets friends who will help her to unfold the mystery which lies<br />
within.</p>

<p>The book left me wondering how the next stories would unfold. It seems as I<br />
was preparing and reading this story for something unbelievable ahead. It<br />
made me think about the societies we live in, the rights we own, and how<br />
the goverment can affect those they govern. People have the right to know<br />
the truth behind governing. The government should allow proper rights to<br />
its people and use power accordingly. Only then the society would function.<br />
</p><div>Gathering Blue  by Lois Lowry is the second book in The Giver Quartet. Just like the first book, this book sets in the same future time. <div><br /></div><div>In the future there&#39;s a villege, a confounded villege where no one can express freedom. People are drilled with chores, and heavily damaged in many ways. Kira, a strong and courageous girl faces her life with audacity. Kira is born with a deformed leg. When her mother dies, she is left with nothing. Her mother had taught her how to weave, work with thread since she was young. The skill of weaving &quot;came&quot; to her as long as she can remember and this ability allows her to land on an important job. Throughout the story, she meets friends who will help her to unfold the mystery which lies within. <div><br /></div><div>The book left me wondering how the next stories would unfold. It seems as I was preparing and reading this story for something unbelievable ahead. It made me think about the societies we live in, the rights we own, and how the goverment can affect those they govern. People have the right to know the truth behind governing. The government should allow proper rights to its people and use power accordingly. Only then the society would function.</div></div></div>
]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>Weather</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/2017/02/weather.html" />
    <id>tag:blog.youre.space,2017:/imyagirl//17.527</id>

    <published>2017-02-26T08:51:46Z</published>
    <updated>2017-02-26T14:41:20Z</updated>

    <summary>The strange effect the weather has on a person is intriguing. Lately, somewhere between the winter and spring have dawned upon us. The short month of February brought various kinds of weather, from cold air to warm sunshine. On a...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Ella Chung</name>
        
    </author>
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/">
        <![CDATA[<p>The strange effect the weather has on a person is intriguing. Lately, somewhere between the winter and spring have dawned upon us. The short month of February brought various kinds of weather, from cold air to warm sunshine. On a sunny day, a person might feel warmth or hope. The cold, windy days make us realize the winter is not ready to leave us just yet. The cold wind brushes upon our faces, less willing inside.</p>
<p>Lately, the dusty days have been occuring more than all of us like. The warmer the days get, the heavier the dusts get. On a warm, sunny day, where people ought to enjoy themselves, are bothered by dusts changing the way we feel. Not being able to breathe in the fresh air we all desire, only leaves confusion and hatred.</p>
<p>The nature has its own way of giving us the grateful feeling inside. As the new season nears, hoping we would be able to savor every bit of the weather.</p>]]>
        
    </content>
</entry>

<entry>
    <title>첫번째</title>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/2017/01/post.html" />
    <id>tag:blog.youre.space,2017:/imyagirl//17.473</id>

    <published>2017-01-30T15:31:41Z</published>
    <updated>2017-01-31T14:36:17Z</updated>

    <summary>글입니다. 앞으로 여보가 글 많이 써줄 겁니다. 흐흫...</summary>
    <author>
        <name>Ella Chung</name>
        
    </author>
    
    
    <content type="html" xml:lang="en-us" xml:base="http://weblog.youre.space/imyagirl/">
        글입니다. 앞으로 여보가 글 많이 써줄 겁니다. 흐흫
        
    </content>
</entry>

</feed>
